<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wisdom of Sun Tzu</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="quote1">Politics means the thing which causes the people to be in harmony with there ruler so they will follow him in disregard of their lives and without fear of any danger.</string>
    <string name="quote2">Doctrine consists of gradation of rank among officers, regulation of supply routes and provision of military materials to an army.</string>
    <string name="quote3">All warfare is based on deception. Prepare against the enemy when he is secure at all points. Attack him where he is unprepared.</string>
    <string name="quote4">To subdue the enemy without fighting is the supreme excellence.</string>
    <string name="quote5">Politics means the thing which causes the people to be in harmony with there ruler so they will follow him in disregard of their lives and without fear of any danger.</string>
    <string name="quote6">Doctrine consists of gradation of rank among officers, regulation of supply routes and provision of military materials to an army.</string>
    <string name="quote7">All warfare is based on deception. Prepare against the enemy when he is secure at all points. Attack him where he is unprepared.</string>
    <string name="quote8">Speedy victory is the main object in war.</string>
    <string name="quote9">When your strength is exhausted and your treasure spent, other chieftains will spring up to take advantage of your crisis to act.</string>
    <string name="quote10">Bring war material with you from home, but forage on the enemy. Thus the army will have food enough for its needs.</string>
    <string name="quote11">Mix captured chariots with your own. Treat prisoners of war well. This is called "winning the battle and becoming stronger".</string>
    <string name="quote12">In war let your great object be victory, not lengthy campaigns.</string>
    <string name="quote13"> To subdue the enemy without fighting is the supreme excellence.</string>
    <string name="quote14">The highest form of generalship is to balk the enemy\'s plans; the next best is to prevent the junction of the enemy\'s forces; the next in order is to attack the enemy's army in the field; and the worst policy of all is to besiege walled cities.</string>
    <string name="quote15">Interference from an ignorant sovereign will bring misfortune on his army.</string>
    <string name="quote16">If you know the enemy and know yourself, you need not fear the result of a hundred battles.</string>
    <string name="quote17">Invincibility depends on ones self, but the enemies vulnerability depends on him.</string>
    <string name="quote18">Defend your self when you cannot defeat the enemy, and attack the enemy when you can.</string>
    <string name="quote19">The skillful fighter puts himself into a position which makes defeat impossible. The victorious strategist only seeks battle after the victory has been won.</string>
    <string name="quote20">The consummate leader cultivates their policies, and strictly adhere to the laws and regulation.</string>
    <string name="quote21">The control of a large force is the same principle as the control of a few men: it is merely a question of organisation.</string>
    <string name="quote22">Use ordinary forces to engage and extraordinary forces to win.</string>
    <string name="quote23">A skilled commander seeks victory from the situation and does not demand it from his subordinates, He selects suitable men and exploits the situation.</string>
    <string name="quote24">Whoever is first in the field and awaits the coming of the enemy, will be fresh for the fight; whoever is second in the field and has to hasten to battle will arrive exhausted.</string>
    <string name="quote25">The spot where we intend to fight must not be made known; for then the enemy will have to prepare against attack in great many places.</string>
    <string name="quote26">In war, the way is to avoid what is strong and to strike at what is weak.</string>
    <string name="quote27">If I concentrate forces while he divides, I can use my entire force to attack a fraction of his.</string>
    <string name="quote28">Avoid the enemy when his spirit is keen and attack him when it is sluggish.</string>
    <string name="quote29">If one orders his men to make forced marches it is probable the commander will be captured.</string>
    <string name="quote30">You should not encamp on grounds hard to approach. Unite with your allies on ground intersected with highways.</string>
    <string name="quote31">There are some grounds which should not be contested.</string>
    <string name="quote32">5 Fatal Qualities of a Commander: Recklessness, Cowardliness, Quick-Tempered, delicate sense of honour and compassionate.</string>
    <string name="quote33">Do not assume the enemy will come but rather rely on ones readiness to meet him.</string>
    <string name="quote34">Position yourself on the high ground with the sun at your back.</string>
    <string name="quote35">If officers are short-tempered they are exhausted.</string>
    <string name="quote36">If officers first treat men violently and later fear them it shows supreme lack of intelligence.</string>
    <string name="quote37">If troops are punished before their loyalty is secured they will become disobedient.</string>
    <string name="quote38">If soldiers are strong and the officers are weak an army is insubordinate. If the soldiers are valiant and the officers are ineffective the result is collapse.</string>
    <string name="quote39">A general should treat his soldiers like his own beloved sons and they will follow him until death. If he is unable to control them they can be compared to spoiled children and they are useless.</string>
    <string name="quote40">Attack the enemy where he has taken no precautions.</string>
    <string name="quote41">Throw your soldiers into positions whence there is no escape,and they will prefer death to flight. If they will face death, there is nothing they may not achieve.</string>
    <string name="quote42">It is the business of a general to be quiet and thus ensure secrecy; upright and just, and thus maintain order.</string>
    <string name="quote43">At first exhibit the shyness of a maiden, until the enemy gives you an opening; afterwards emulate the rapidity of a running hare, and it will be too late for the enemy to oppose you.</string>
    <string name="quote44">If you cannot succeed do not employ troops, if you are not in danger do not fight a war.</string>
    <string name="quote45">What enables the wise sovereign and the good general to strike and conquer, and achieve things beyond the reach of ordinary men, is foreknowledge.</string>
    <string name="quote46">Spy operations are essential in war; upon them the army relies to make its avery move.</string>
</resources>
